Hey! You're not gonna believe this.
Yes, Ross, we know they have magazines
with pictures of naked women in them.
Don't tell him about the videos!
I made up a joke
and sent it in to Playboy.
They printed it.
I didn't know they print jokes.
They print jokes, interviews,
hard-hitting journalism.
It's not just about the pictures.
Didn't work on Mom,
it's not gonna work on us.
Check it out. It's the first one.
Right there.
That is funny.
It was also funny when I made it up.
-What?
-I made that joke up.
No, you didn't. I did.
Yes, I did. I told Dan and he said it
was the funniest joke he'd ever heard.
Hey, tell Dan thanks.
What?
I was just reading the joke below it.
Man, that one is funny.
Monica, you remember me
telling you that joke, right?
-No.
-Seriously?
You tell a lot of jokes.
Look, it's my joke.
But if it makes you feel better,
they don't print the name.
So it doesn't really matter
who gets credit.
Yeah, I guess.
-Hey, guys.
-Playboy printed my joke!
No, it's mine! Call them!
They'll tell you!
-My joke!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Jokes? What...?
You know there's naked chicks
in there, right?
The One With The Joke
Dude! You have got to turn on
Behind The Music.
The band Heart is having a tough
time and they may break up.
Let's watch that at your place.
Monica's watching a show. I don't
want to miss when they were skinny.
Hey, Chandler?
You know what we should do?
You and I should go out
and get some new sunglasses.
What? No, I want to watch this.
-Did your cable go out?
-No. No, that's VH1.
I tell you, the music
these kids listen to today...
it's a lot of noise to me.
Why is your cable out?
Oh, because I haven't really
paid the bill.
If you need money,
would you please let me loan you some?
No, Chandler. Forget about it, okay?
I know things have been tight since
Janine moved out. God, was she hot.
I know, yeah.
Look, I can handle it, all right?
I can listen to the radio.
And Ross gave me this great book.
Want to see if the joke stealer
will let us watch at his place?
Sure.
-Paid your phone bill?
-No.
It's only you.
-What are you doing?
-Looking at a Playboy.
I want to look too!
Yikes!
Do you think these pictures
are trying to tell a story?
Sure. Like in the case
of this young woman...
she has lost her clothes.
So she rides naked on the horse,
she's crying out, "Where are they?"
She's not gonna find them,
lying in the grass like that.
Remember the days when you'd
go out to the barn...
Lift up your shirt and bend over?
You see, now, I would date this girl.
She's cute, she's outdoorsy.
And she knows how to build a fire.
That'll come in handy.
I got a question.
If you had to pick one of us to date,
who would it be?
-I don't know.
-Me neither.
Rachel.
What?
I don't know.
Me neither.
You know, you forget how many
great songs Heart had.
"Barracuda" was the first song
I learned to play on the keyboard.
So you heard it, you repeated it...
so that must mean you wrote it.
You guys with this joke.
Well, I gotta say...
I know I cracked up,
but I'm not even sure I got it.
What?
You didn't get it?
The doctor is a monkey.
And monkeys
can't write out prescriptions.
You are not allowed
to laugh at my joke.
Your joke?
Well, I think the Hef
would disagree.
Which is why he sent me a check...
for $100.
So you stole my joke
and you stole my money?
I was gonna stick it in the ATM.
But now I think I'll show
the sexy teller...
that I am a published writer.
She'll know that you stole the joke.
You gonna follow me there?
-Yeah.
-I'm not gonna go now.
Okay.
Here you go.
Gunther?
I can't pay now,
because I'm not working.
I've had to cut down
on some luxuries like...
paying for stuff, so....
Well, if you want, you can work here.
I don't know.
It's just....
See, I was a regular on a soap opera,
you know?
And to go from that to this,
it's just....
And plus, I'd have to wait
on all my friends.
Okay. But the money's good.
Plus, you get to stare at Rachel
as much as you want.
What?
Flexible hours.
Maybe I could be a waiter.
Could I use the phone?
She picked Rachel.
She tried to back out of it, but
it was obvious. She picked Rachel.
He took my joke. He just took it.
This is wrong.
You know what else is wrong?
Phoebe picking Rachel.
Know who else picked Rachel? Ross.
Know what else Ross did?
He stole my joke.
I'm gonna get a joke journal,
you know?
And document the date and time
of every single one of my jokes.
Good idea. Know what's a bad idea?
-Picking Rachel.
-That's right.
Did you hear something?
Maybe it's the sound of Ross climbing
into my brain to steal my thoughts.
It's coming from the living room.
I finished my book.
-Hey, you guys.
-Hey.
Don't you guys look cute.
You guys make a cute couple.
What are you doing?
Just trying to re-create some of
the fun that we had at my place.
Remember? When you picked
Rachel over me?
That was funny.
-It was kind of funny.
-It wasn't funny at all!
Why would you do that?
Why didn't you pick me?
Fine.
The reason I was leaning a little
bit more toward Rachel than you...
is just, you know, you're...
high maintenance.
Let's go to lunch!
That is completely untrue.
You think I'm high maintenance?
Prove it.
You write out a list, and
we'll go through it point by point.
No, you're right, you're easygoing.
You're just not as easygoing
as Rachel. She's just more...
flexible and mellow. That's all.
Well, people are different.
Rachel will do whatever you want.
You can just walk all over her.
What? Are you saying that I'm
a pushover? I'm not a pushover.
Oh, okay. You're not a pushover.
You think I'm a pushover.
Well, watch this.
You're not invited to lunch!
What do you think?
Pretty strong, I think.
Come on, Monica, let's go to lunch.
You start working on that list.
-I cannot believe her.
-I know. Where do you want to eat?
-Oh, I love that Japanese place.
-I'm sick of Japanese. Not there.
Wherever you want to go is cool.
Oh, hey, Gunther...
check this out.
Yeah, that Chandler cracks me up.
You want anything to drink?
I'm heading up there.
-I'll take a coffee. Thanks.
-Sure.
-Coffee?
-No.
Coffee? I'm going up there.
No, thank you.
You need anything?
I'm heading up there.
I'd love ice water.
You got it.
What are you doing?
Just being friendly.
You're not supposed to go back there.
It's okay. Right?
Don't wink at me.
And put on your apron.
Okay.
I don't see you asking other
paying customers to put on aprons.
-Joey, do you work here?
-No.
-Waiter.
-Yeah!
What's going on?
Why didn't you tell us you work here?
It's kind of embarrassing. I mean,
I was an actor, now I'm a waiter.
It's supposed to go
the other direction.
So's your apron.
You're wearing it like a cape.
I mean, the job's easy
and the money's good, you know?
I guess if I'm hanging out here,
I might as well get paid for it.
I just feel kind of weird
serving you guys, you know?
It'll be great.
Come on, I did it and it was fine.
Why would it be weird?
Hey, Joey? Can I get some coffee?
It doesn't seem that weird.
I asked before.
You still haven't gotten it.
See, now it's weird again.
You're gonna make a lot of money.
Here's your first tip.
Don't eat yellow snow.
2:15, coffeehouse.
This is great. Finally,
someone I can pass my wisdom to.
Let me tell you some things
I learned working here.
First, the customer is always right.
A smile goes a long way.
And if anyone is ever rude to you,
sneeze muffin.
Thanks, Rach.
Hey, look, you guys are just terrific,
you know?
How about clearing out
so I can get some new customers?
It's all about turnover.
Seriously, can I get my coffee?
I'm sorry. I'll get it right now.
And since you waited,
I'll toss in a free muffin.
Phoebe, we'd like to talk to you.
Okay.
So, maybe I am
a little high maintenance.
And maybe Rachel is
a little bit of a pushover.
But you know what you are?
We are sorry to tell you this,
but you, Phoebe, are flaky.
That's true, I am flaky.
So, what, you're just okay
with being flaky?
Yeah, totally.
Then I'm okay
with being high maintenance.
Yeah. And I am okay
with being a pushover.
That's great. Good for you guys.
-I am not high maintenance!
-I am not a pushover!
-Who said you were?
-You did!
I'm flaky. I'll say anything.
Hey, Gunther.
Can you cover for me?
I got an audition.
No, I'm leaving to get my hair dyed.
I like your natural color.
It's a great part.
I'm the lead guy's best friend.
I wait for him and save his seat.
Listen.
"I'm sorry, that seat's saved."
-That's the whole part?
-Maybe he's not his best friend.
I'll see you.
Oh, man.
I could totally get that part.
"I'm sorry, this seat is taken."
-Excuse me.
-No, I didn't mean you.
But you believed me?
I believed you were saving this seat
for someone.
So you'd hire me, right?
For what?
Exactly!
All right, everybody listen up!
The coffeehouse will be closed
for about an hour.
What?
It's for the kids.
Yeah, to keep the kids off drugs.
It's a very important issue
in this month's Playboy.
I'm sure you all read about it.
Hey! Don't you wanna keep guns
away from kids?
-You said, "drugs."
-It's a vicious cycle. Get out!
Go!
-It's my joke.
It's my joke.
I don't think we're gonna settle this.
Let's have Monica decide.
-Hey, Mon!
-Get out here!
-Monica?
-Okay.
You have to decide whose joke this is.
Why do I have to?
You're the only one that can be fair.
I can't be. You're my boyfriend.
But I'm your brother. We're family.
That's the most important thing
in the world.
Don't try to sway her.
I'm your only chance to have a baby.
-Okay, let's go.
-All right.
We'll each tell you
how we came up with the joke...
then you decide which one of us
is telling the truth. Me.
Chandler, you first.
I thought of the joke two months ago
at lunch with Steve.
-Did I meet him at Christmas?
-Can I finish?
You want me to pick you?
See, I would never
snap at you like that.
Two babies.
-Continue.
-Okay.
Steve said he had to go to the doctor.
And his doctor's name is Dr. Mompey.
I said, "Dr. Monkey?" And that is how
the whole Dr. Monkey thing came up.
Are you kidding?
Okay, look, I study evolution.
Remember? Evolution.
Monkey into man.
Plus, I'm a doctor. And...
I had a monkey.
I'm Dr. Monkey!
I'm not arguing with that.
I've heard enough for my decision.
-Okay, so what..?
-Do tell.
You are both idiots.
It's not funny.
And it's offensive to women.
And doctors. And monkeys.
You shouldn't argue
over who gets credit.
You should argue over who gets blamed
for inflicting this joke on the world.
Now, let it go.
The joke sucks.
-It's your joke.
-It is not.
-Oh, my God, Chandler, there you are.
-Hi.
Hey, it's Phoebe and Rachel.
Why don't you tell them...
what you told me about me
not being high maintenance.
Monica is a self-sufficient,
together lady.
Being with her
has been like being on a vacation.
And what may be perceived
as high maintenance...
is merely attention to detail...
and...
generosity of spirit.
Wow. You know what? That is the best
fake speech I think I've ever heard.
Really? I've heard better.
Wait, he came up with that himself.
Tell them.
I'm out of words.
Should I say it again?
Look, I am not high maintenance!
I am not. Chandler!
You're a little high maintenance.
You are on my list!
Look, I'm sorry, but you're not..
You're not easygoing,
but you're passionate.
And that's good.
And when you get upset about little
things, I think I'm pretty good...
at making you feel better.
That's good too.
They say you're high maintenance...
but it's okay, because I like...
maintaining you.
I didn't tell him that.
-You're off my list.
-I'm off the list.
Phoebe?
It's okay that you don't want me
to be your girlfriend.
I have the best boyfriend.
You know,
suddenly I find you very attractive.
How'd the audition go?
Oh, not good. No.
I didn't get the part.
And I lost my job here, so...
Wow, that is a bad audition.
Well, how did you lose your job here?
I had the audition...
but Gunther said I had to stay
so he could get his hair dyed.
So I went anyway, and he fired me.
He left work
to do a personal errand...
and left you in charge
when you've been here two days?
That's not right.
What are you gonna do?
You can't let him get away with that.
I won't let him get away with that.
I'm gonna say..
I shouldn't say anything.
No, I should say something!
Gunther?
I want you to give Joey his job back.
-It's not fair that you have to fire..
-Okay.
-What?
-He can have his job back.
That's right,
he can have his job back.
Glad we got that all straightened out.
There you go, Joey.
-Got your job back.
-That's great. Thanks.
Pretty nice, huh?
Now who's a pushover?
-Rach, you're in my seat.
-I'm sorry.
I never heard who you'd pick
to be your girlfriend.
-I'd pick you, Phoebe.
-Yeah, definitely you, Phoebe.
Yeah, I kind of thought.
-Never.
-It would totally be you.
If you had to pick one
of the other two to go out with...
who would you pick?
-No way.
-I'm not answering.
Joey.
No way, I'm not answering that.